

ABOUT ME

An open-minded, self motivated professional with 1.5+ years of experience in managing different social media platforms.

Experienced in interacting with clients, tracking analytics and promoting products. Strong knowledge of Google tools and social media platforms such as Facebook, Instagram, Youtube, Dailymotion. Managed to expand Everest Shoes online by building successful social strategies that resulted in increasing their sales by 15%.

LINKS

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/tasevskialeksandar/

LANGUAGES

MACEDONIAN

ENGLISH

SERBIAN

GERMAN

SPANISH

ALEKSANDAR TASEVSKI

SOCIAL MEDIA MANAGER. VIDEO CONTENT SPECIALIST

4	
	0
	V

Prohor Pchinjski 35, Bitola, 7000, North Macedonia



+389 70 980 210



aleksandar_tasevski@outlook.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

EVEREST SHOES

Bitola

May 2020 - Dec 2021

Social Media Marketing Manager

- Expanded the business online, created and provided content, including logo, images and text posts on social media (Facebook);
- Promoted products, including ads promotions that resulted in increasing the sales by 15%;
- Monitored social analysis, kept track of insights, built successful social strategies, targeting specific group of customers, suitable for the business;
- Interacted with customers and dealt with customer's requirements.

Jul 2011 - Feb 2013

Video Creator

- Gained a lot of knowledge about video platforms (Youtube, Dailymotion etc.);
- Created and published custom made videos on various video platforms;
- Gained an advanced knowledge of Youtube's Terms of Service.

EDUCATION

Skopje Sep 2015 - Present

Bitola Sep 2011 - May 2015 Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering - Skopje

High School "Josip Broz Tito" - Btiola

SKILLS

YOUTUBE, DAILYMOTION, VIMEO

VERBAL AND WRITTEN COMMUNICATION

GOOGLE ANALYTICS, DOCS, SHEETS

FLEXIBILITY/ADAPTABILITY

FACEBOOK, INSTAGRAM, PINTEREST, TIKTOK

PHOTOSHOP

PROBLEM-SOLVING

SOCIAL MEDIA ADVERTISING

CREATIVITY